[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":35353,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":41850,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":11272,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":53131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2101,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":55237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4025,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":59266,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1499,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":60769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":5379,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":66151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1474,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":67629,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":72057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1536,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":73595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or b igger, y ou subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3028,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":76625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1280,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":77907,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3449,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":81360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1060,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":82422,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":85670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1024,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":86697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<s ub>6</su b>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3460,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":90158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1073,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":91234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3502,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":94738,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1200,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":95940,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3151,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":99092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2112,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":101206,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":17477,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":118693,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its o wn inver se under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":36701,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":155399,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":7204,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":162607,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1148,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":163759,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the  thing wh ich you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5133,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":168895,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1128,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":170026,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2642,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":172671,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The i nverse o f 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1301,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":173975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2798,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":176775,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":955,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":177732,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember,  the inve rse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3738,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":181472,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1016,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":182492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":15604,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":198099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn  today,  using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":47166,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":245267,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":10054,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":255326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1371,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":256700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":3350,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":260052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 =  5, 4 = 5  +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1280,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":261335,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4718,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":266056,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6< /sub> 4,  but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1003,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":267062,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2925,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":269989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1053,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":271045,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exac tly like  +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":12421,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":283467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4482,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":287951,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1017,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":288970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4434,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":293406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":6606,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":300014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":3292,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":303309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4096,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":307411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4802,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":312218,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5; 4 + 1 is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so 5 is the answer. ","response_history":["5; 4 +_","5; 4 + 1 is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so 5 s the ","5; 4 + 1 is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so 5 s","5; 4 + 1 is 5 and 5 is less than 9 so 5 is the answer. "],"rt":27245,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":339466,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3; 8 + 4 = 12; subtract 9 because 12 is greater than 9 to get 3. ","response_history":["3; 8 + 4 = 12 - 9","3; 8 + 4 = 12 - ","3; 8 + 4 = 12 -","3; 8 + 4 = 12 ","3; 8 + 4 = 12; sub","3; 8 + 4 = 12; sutra","3; 8 + 4 = 12; sutr","3; 8 + 4 = 12; sut","3; 8 + 4 = 12; subtract 9 because 12 is greater than 9 o","3; 8 + 4 = 12; subtract 9 because 12 is greater than 9 to get 3. "],"rt":35934,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":375404,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"8; because 1 + 8 will equal 9 minus 9 will give you 0","response_history":["1;because ","1;because","1;becaus","1;becau","1;beca","1;bec","1;be","1;b","1;","1","8; because 1 + 8 will equal 9 minus 9 will give you 0"],"rt":42986,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":418393,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":8215,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":426614,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4806,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":431425,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6; 6+3=9; 9-9=0","response_history":["6; 6+3=9; 9=","6; 6+3=9; 9-9=0"],"rt":18275,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":449703,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because adding to 2 will not give you number. ","response_history":["no, beacuse ","no, beacuse","no, beacus","no, beacu","no, beac","no, bea","no, bea","no, bev","no, because addn","no, because adding to 2 will not give you nub","no, because adding to 2 will not give you number. "],"rt":21997,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":471704,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes; because 3+6=9","response_history":["yes; becasue ","yes; becasue","yes; becasu","yes; becas","yes; because 3+6=9"],"rt":12006,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":483714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no; because 5+1 does not equal 9","response_history":["no; becasue ","no; becasue","no; becasu","no; becas","no; because 5+1 does not equal 9"],"rt":21826,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":505543,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because 6+3=9","response_history":["yes, beca","yes, bec","yes, because 6+3=9"],"rt":14514,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":520062,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub >, where  n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":31836,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":551903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1_n","response_history":["1_n"],"rt":37308,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":589215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x_n; x could stand for any positive number _n","response_history":["x_n; x vou","x_n; x vo","x_n; x v","x_n; x could stand for any number ","x_n; x could stand for any number","x_n; x could stand for any numbe","x_n; x could stand for any numb","x_n; x could stand for any num","x_n; x could stand for any nu","x_n; x could stand for any n","x_n; x could stand for any positive number _n"],"rt":27653,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":616872,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It must be a positive number, That is the only pattern I can find.","response_history":["It must be a positive number, That is the only pattern I can find ","It must be a positive number, That is the only pattern I can find."],"rt":26768,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":643644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4568,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":648216,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4881,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":653104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"Fal se","response_history":["False"],"rt":6035,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":659142,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I believe that there would be nothing that could be divided by n to be a generator. ","response_history":["I believe that there would be nothing that could be divided o","I believe that there would be nothing that could be divided to ","I believe that there would be nothing that could be divided to","I believe that there would be nothing that could be divided t","I believe that there would be nothing that could be divided by n to be a gen","I believe that there would be nothing that could be divided by n to be a geen","I believe that there would be nothing that could be div ided by  n to be a geen","I believe that there would be nothing that could be divided by n to be a gee","I believe that there would be nothing that could be divided by n to be a generator. "],"rt":36535,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":695680,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11095,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":706778,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes; it depends on what x is.","response_history":["Sometimes ","Sometimes; it depends on the mu","Sometimes; it depends on the m","Sometimes; it depends on the ","Sometimes; it depends on the","Sometimes; it depends on th","Sometimes; it depends on t","Sometimes; it depends on what x is ","Sometimes; it depends on what x is."],"rt":21905,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":728686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11408,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":740098,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some question s about  your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2627,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":742728,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","response_history":["32"],"rt":2890,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":745620,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Associates Degree","response_history":["Associates Degree"],"rt":2223,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":747848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the  most ad vanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus","response_history":["Calu","Calcilus","Calcilu","Calcil","Calci","Calculus"],"rt":17481,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":765334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":5315,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":770654,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":4727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":775385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3157,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":778546,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in t his HIT? ","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3427,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":781975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2640,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":784619,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":3826,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":788447,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your n ative la nguage(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","response_history":["english"],"rt":4711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":793161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no; although I wish I had as I feel like I was getting inverse and generator confused when it came to creating the formula and determining x as a generator or inverse? ","response_history":["no; although I wish I had as I feel like I was getter","no; although I wish I had as I feel like I was getteing ","no; although I wish I had as I feel like I was getteing","no; although I wish I had as I feel like I was gettein","no; although I wish I had as I feel like I was gettei","no; although I wish I had as I feel like I w as gette ","no; although I wish I had as I feel like I was getting inverse and generator confused when it came to creating the formula and determine","no; although I wish I had as I feel like I was getting inverse and generator confused when it came to creating the formula and determining x a ","no; although I wish I had as I feel like I was getting inverse and generator confused when it came to creating the formula and determining x as a generator or inverse? "],"rt":41570,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":834735,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have gone back to review the information. Overall a really interesting Hit where I feel like I may have l earned a  little something. ","response_history":["Sorry id ","Sorry id","Sorry if some of my s","Sorry if some of my answer ","Sorry if some of my answers swee","Sorry if some of my answers swe","Sorry if some of my answers sw","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I rel","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I reallyy ","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I reallyy","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I reall","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concenpt ","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concenpt","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concenp","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concen","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway w","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really  tried to  understand the concept until midway through when I stra","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I str","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to foget ","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to foget","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to foge","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to fog","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I o","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forg et the d efinitions and wished I could an","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could a","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have co","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have c","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have gone back to review he ","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have gone back to review he","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I  really t ried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have gone back to review h","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have gone back to review the informaton. Overall a really intersting Hit where I feel like I may have learnie","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have gone back to review the informaton. Overall a really intersting Hit where I feel like I may have learni","Sorry if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have gone back to review the informaton. Overall a really intersting Hit where I feel like I may have learned a little something.  ","Sorry  if some of my answers seemed random. I really tried to understand the concept until midway through when I started to forget the definitions and wished I could have gone back to review the information. Overall a really interesting Hit where I feel like I may have learned a little something. "],"rt":74618,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":909359,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]